Daniel C. Dennett Papers MS138
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Writings, 1958 -- 2015; MS138.001; 4.15 Linear Feet; 415 Digital Object(s)
  - Review of The Symbolic Species: The Co-Evolution of Language the Brain, by Terrence Deacon [and] Le Ton Beau de Marot: In Praise of the Music of Language, by Douglas Hofstadter, 1997; MS138.001.002.00125; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - What is Thinking?, 1997; MS138.001.002.00126; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Comments on Artificial Intelligence (web dialogue), 1997 -- 2005; MS138.001.002.00127; Dennett, Daniel C.; Dreyfus, Hubert
    - Comments on Artificial Intelligence (web dialogue), 1997; MS138.001.002.00127.00001; Dennett, Daniel C.; Dreyfus, Hubert (Box 2)
    - La vittoria di Deep Blue su Kasparov dimostra il successo dell'Intelligenzia Artificiale? [Italian translation of Comments on Artificial Intelligence (web dialogue)], 1997; MS138.001.002.00127.00002; Dennett, Daniel C.; Dreyfus, Hubert (Box 2)
    - Did Deep Blue's Win over Kasparov Prove That Artificial Intelligence Has Succeeded?: A Debate, 2005; MS138.001.002.00127.00003; Dennett, Daniel C.; Dreyfus, Hubert (Box 2)
  - Consciousness in Human and Robot Minds, 1997; MS138.001.002.00128; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - How to Do Other Things with Words, 1997; MS138.001.002.00129; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Cartesian theater; Austin, J. L. (John Langshaw), 1911-1960.
  - Can Machines Think? Deep Blue and Beyond, 1997; MS138.001.002.00130; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Cog as a Thought Experiment, 1997; MS138.001.002.00131; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Evolutionary Psychology: An Exchange, 1997; MS138.001.002.00132; Gould, Stephen Jay; Kalant, Harold; Kalow, Werner; Pinker, Steven (Box 2)
  - The Case of the Tell-Tale Traces: A Mystery Solved; a Skyhook Grounded, 1997; MS138.001.002.00133; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Our Mind's Chief Asset: Review of Being There, by Andy Clark, 1997; MS138.001.002.00134; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Cognition; Embodied cognition
  - La coscienza: un eterno enigma filosofico [Italian interview with Daniel Dennett], 1997; MS138.001.002.00135; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Curiousity - 'Epistemic Hunger', 1997; MS138.001.002.00136; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Is Your Mind in Your Brain?, 1997 -- 1999; MS138.001.002.00137; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Is Your Mind in Your Brain?, 1997; MS138.001.002.00137.00001; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Is Your Mind in Your Brain?, 1997; MS138.001.002.00137.00002; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - La mente sta nel cervello? [Italian translation of Is Your Mind in Your Brain?], 1999; MS138.001.002.00137.00003; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Brainchildren: Essays on Designing Minds, 1998; MS138.001.002.00138; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - The Myth of Double Transduction, 1998; MS138.001.002.00139; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - The Myth of Double Transduction, 1998; MS138.001.002.00139.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    - Il mito della doppia trasduzione [Italian translation of The Myth of Double Transduction], 1998; MS138.001.002.00139.00003; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Comment on A Critique of Evolutionary Archeology, by James L. Boone and Eric Alden Smith, 1998; MS138.001.002.00140; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Natural selection; Artificial Selection; Memetics; Cultural evolution
  - The Evolution of Religious Memes: Who or What Benefits?, 1998; MS138.001.002.00141; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Author's Response to Overlooked Skyhooks, 1998; MS138.001.002.00142; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Reflections on Language and Mind, 1998; MS138.001.002.00143; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Language of thought; Cartesian theater; Information Processing; Semantics; Modularity (psychology)
  - An Interview with Fred Dretske, 1998; MS138.001.002.00145; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Artificial Evolution In Virtual and Real World Setting, 1998; MS138.001.002.00146; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Memes: Myths, Misgivings, Misunderstandings, 1998 -- 2002; MS138.001.002.00147; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Memes: Myths, Misgivings, Misunderstandings, 1998; MS138.001.002.00147.00001; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Memes: Mitos, más compreens_es e más atribuiço_s [Portuguese translation of Memes: Myths, Misgivings, Misunderstandings], 2001; MS138.001.002.00147.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    - Mémek: Mítoszok, Félreértések és félelmek [Hungarian translation of Memes: Myths, Misgivings, Misunderstandings], 2002; MS138.001.002.00147.00003; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Minds and Machines: An Interview with Daniel C. Dennett, 1998; MS138.001.002.00148; Dennett, Daniel C.; Madigan, Tim (Box 2)
  - No Bridge Over the Stream of Consciousness, 1998; MS138.001.002.00149; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Preston on Exaptation: Herons, Apples, and Eggs, 1998-11; MS138.001.002.00150; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Natural selection; Adaptationism; Preston, Beth
  - Reply to Nicholas Humphrey, Cave Art, Autism, and the Evolution of the Human Mind, 1998; MS138.001.002.00151; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Genetic phsychology; Conciousness; Art, Prehistoric; Autism; Humphrey, Nicholas
  - Revolution, no! Reform, si!, 1998; MS138.001.002.00152; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - The Creation of Creativity, 1998; MS138.001.002.00153; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Stability is Not Intrinsic, 1999; MS138.001.002.00154; Dennett, Daniel C.; Westbury, C. F. (Box 2)
    Consciousness; Connectionism; Content (Psychology)
  - Afterword, 1999; MS138.001.002.00155; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Intentional Stance, 1998; MS138.001.002.00156; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Intentional stance; Intentionality
  - The Virtues of Virtual Machines, 1999; MS138.001.002.00157; Dennett, Daniel C.; Densmore, Shannon (Box 2)
  - Protecting Public Health, 1999; MS138.001.002.00158; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Ludwig Wittgenstein, 1999-03-29; MS138.001.002.00159; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    - Time Magazine: The century's greatest minds, 1999-03-29; MS138.001.002.00159.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
  - Sort-of Symbols?, 1999; MS138.001.002.00160; Dennett, Daniel C.; Viger, Christopher (Box 2)
  - Foreword, 1999; MS138.001.002.00161; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Why Getting it Right Matters, 1999 -- 2000; MS138.001.002.00162; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Why Getting It Right Matters, 1999; MS138.001.002.00162.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    - [Russian translation of Why Getting It Right Matters], 1999; MS138.001.002.00162.00003; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    - Postmodernism and Truth, 2000; MS138.001.002.00162.00004; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
      File also includes correspondence to Dennett from the publisher and an edited draft of the article.
    - [Russian translation of Postmodernism and Truth], 2000; MS138.001.002.00162.00005; Dennett, Daniel C.; Yulina, N.S. (Box 2)
  - Intrinsic Changes in Experience: Swift and Enormous, 1999; MS138.001.002.00163; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Review of Having Thought: Essays in the Metaphysics of Mind, by John Haugeland, 1999; MS138.001.002.00164; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Cognition; Metaphysics; Haugeland, John, 1945-2010
  - Consilience: Letters to the Editor, 1999; MS138.001.002.00165; Dennett, Daniel C.; Viger, Christopher (Box 2)
  - The Battery, 2000; MS138.001.002.00166; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Foreword, 2000; MS138.001.002.00167; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - It's Not a Bug, It's a Feature, 2000; MS138.001.002.00168; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Conciousness; Artificial intelligence; Evolutionary Psychology; Humphrey, Nicholas
  - Making Tools for Thinking, 2000; MS138.001.002.00169; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Re-introducing The Concept of the Mind, a Foreword, 2000; MS138.001.002.00170; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Ryle, Gilbert, 1900-1976
  - The Case for Rorts, 2000; MS138.001.002.00171; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Daniel Dennett's Darwinian Mind: An Interview with a 'Dangerous' Man, 2000; MS138.001.002.00172; Dennett, Daniel C.; Floyd, Chris (Box 2)
  - Interview with Danial Dennett, 2000; MS138.001.002.00173; Dennett, Daniel C.; Junyent, Cristina (Box 2)
  - Interview with Danial Dennett, 2000; MS138.001.002.00174; Dennett, Daniel C.; Bisier, Enrique Font
  - Mining The Past To Construct The Future: Memory and Belief as Forms of Knowledge, 2000; MS138.001.002.00175; Dennett, Daniel C.; Westbury, C. F. (Box 2)
  - With a Little Help from My Friends, 2000; MS138.001.002.00176; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Dennett, Daniel [Russian encyclopedia entry], 2000; MS138.001.002.00177; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Daniel Dennett: Concept of Consciousness and Personhood [Russian article], 2000; MS138.001.002.00178; Dennett, Daniel C.; Yulina, N.S. (Box 2)
  - Are We Explaining Consciousness Yet?, 2001; MS138.001.002.00179; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Conciousness; Conciousness, Mathmatical Models; Neural networks (Neurobiology); Consciousness-Physiological aspects
  - Implantable Brain Chips - Will They Change Who We Are?, 2001; MS138.001.002.00180; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Collision, Detection, Muselot, and Scribble: Some Reflections on Creativity, 2001; MS138.001.002.00181; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Things about Things, 2001; MS138.001.002.00182; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - The Evolution of Culture, 1999 -- 2001; MS138.001.002.00183
    - The Evolution of Culture, 1999; MS138.001.002.00183.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    - The Evolution of Culture, 2001; MS138.001.002.00183.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - The Zombic Hunch: Extinction of an Intuition?, 2001; MS138.001.002.00184; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Consciousness; Naturalism; Functionalism; Chalmers, David John, 1966-; Leibniz, Gottfried Wilhelm, Freiherr von, 1646-1716
  - In Darwin's Wake, Where Am I? (APA Presidential Address), 2001; MS138.001.002.00185; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - In Darwin's Wake, Where Am I? (APA Presidential Address), 2001; MS138.001.002.00185.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    - Russian translation of In Darwin's Wake, Where Am I?, 2001; MS138.001.002.00185.00003; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Review of Breakdown of Will, by George Ainslie, 2001; MS138.001.002.00186; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Will; Choice (Psychology); Self-defeating behavior; Neuroeconomics; Ainslie, George
  - Interview with Daniel Dennett, MS138.001.002.00187; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Hungarian
  - The Evolution of Evaluators, 2001; MS138.001.002.00188; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Surprise, surprise, 2001; MS138.001.002.00189; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Explaining the 'Magic' of Consciousness, 2001 -- 2003; MS138.001.002.00190; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Explaining the 'Magic' of Consciousness, 2001; MS138.001.002.00190.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    - Explaining the 'Magic' of Consciousness, 2002; MS138.001.002.00190.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    - Explaining the 'Magic' of Consciousness, 2003; MS138.001.002.00190.00003; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Dennett: About Postmodernism and Debates with Rorty, 2001; MS138.001.002.00191; Dennett, Daniel C.; Yulina, N.S. (Box 2)
  - The New Replicators, 2002; MS138.001.002.00192; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Commentary on Sober and Wilson, Unto Others: The Evolution and Psychology of Unselfish Behavior, 2002; MS138.001.002.00193; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Whos Afraid of Determinism? Rethinking Causes and Possibilities, 2002; MS138.001.002.00194; Dennett, Daniel C.; Taylor, Christopher (Box 2)
  - How Could I be Wrong? How Wrong Could I Be?, 2002; MS138.001.002.00195; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Gilbert Ryle's Last Letter to Dennett, 2002; MS138.001.002.00196; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - Does your brain use the images in it, and if so, how?, 2002; MS138.001.002.00197; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
    Imagery (psychology); Cartesian theater; Neuroscience; Heterophenomenology; Pylyshyn, Zenon W., 1937-
  - Books of the Year: Reviews of The Blank Slate, by Steven Pinker and Darwins Cathedral, by David Sloan Wilson, 2002; MS138.001.002.00198; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Tarbutniks Rule: Review of Animal Traditions: Behavioural Inheritance in Evolution, by Eytan Avital and Eva Jablonka, 2002; MS138.001.002.00199; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Reply to Clark, 2002; MS138.001.002.00200; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - A Naturalistic Perspective on Intentionality: Interview with Daniel Dennett, 2002; MS138.001.002.00201; Dennett, Daniel C.; Mirolli, Marco (Box 2)
  - Review of Making Ourselves at Home in Our Machines: The Illusion of Conscious Will, by Daniel Wegner, 2002; MS138.001.002.00202; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - To Tell the Truth?, 2001; MS138.001.002.00203; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 2)
  - Freedom Evolves, 2004 -- 2005; MS138.001.003.00001; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - L'evoluzione della libertà [Italian translation of Freedom Evolves], 2004; MS138.001.003.00001.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
    - De evolutie van de vrije wil [Dutch translation of Freedom Evolves], 2004; MS138.001.003.00001.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
    - A Liberdade Evolui [Portugese translation of Freedom Evolves], 2005; MS138.001.003.00001.00003; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
    - A Liberdade Evolui [Portugese translation of Freedom Evolves], 2005; MS138.001.003.00001.00004; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
  - The Baldwin Effect: A Crane, Not a Skyhook, 2003; MS138.001.003.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    Baldwin effect; Natural selection; Genetic assimilation; Godfrey-Smith, Peter; Waddington, C. H. (Conrad Hal), 1905-1975
  - Postscript on the Balwin Effect and Niche Construction, 2003; MS138.001.003.00003; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - The Mythical Threat of Genetic Determinisim, 2003; MS138.001.003.00004; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - On Failures of Freedom and the Fear of Science, 2003; MS138.001.003.00005; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Look Out for the Dirty Baby, 2003; MS138.001.003.00006; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    Behaviorism; Conciousness; Baars, Bernard J.; Skinner, B. F.
  - The Bright Stuff, 2003; MS138.001.003.00007; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    File contains a printout of the online version of Dennett's article.
  - Who's on First? Heterophenomenology Explained, 2003; MS138.001.003.00008; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    Heterophenomenology; Conciousness; Introspection; Subjectivity; Intentional stance
  - Review of Radiant Cool, by Dan Lloyd and Love and Other Games of Chance, by Lee Siegel, 2003; MS138.001.003.00009; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Beyond Beanbag Semantics, 2003; MS138.001.003.00010; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Forestalling a Food Fight Over Color, 2003; MS138.001.003.00011; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - The Self as a Respondingand ResponsibleArtifact, 2003; MS138.001.003.00012; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Free Will, But Not As We Know It, 2003; MS138.001.003.00013; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Review of Making Ourselves at Home in Our Machines: The Illusion of Conscious Will, by Daniel Wegner, 2003; MS138.001.003.00014; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Reply to Commentators, 2003; MS138.001.003.00015; Baars, Bernard J. (Box 3)
  - Shame on Rea, 2003; MS138.001.003.00016; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    File contains a draft version of Dennett's response.
  - Interview with Daniel Dennett, 2004; MS138.001.003.00017; Dennett, Daniel C.; Horowitz, Eli (Box 3)
  - The Seed Salon: A Dialogue with E.O. Wilson and Daniel Dennett, 2004; MS138.001.003.00018; Dennett, Daniel C.; Wilson, Edward O., Dr. (Box 3)
  - Obituary, John Maynard Smith, 2004; MS138.001.003.00019; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    Evolution; Natural selection; Maynard Smith, John, 1920-
  - Consciousness, 2004; MS138.001.003.00020; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - What I Want To Be When I Grow Up, 2004; MS138.001.003.00021; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Holding A Mirrow Up to Dupre: Commentary on John Dupre's Human Nature and The Limits of Science, 2004; MS138.001.003.00022; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - An Evolutionary Perspective on Cognition: Through a Glass Lightly, 2004; MS138.001.003.00023; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - 'Epiphenomenal Qualia?, 2004; MS138.001.003.00024; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Calling the Cartesian Loans, 2004; MS138.001.003.00025; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - The Semantic Engineer: A Profile of Daniel Dennett, 2004; MS138.001.003.00026; Dennett, Daniel C.; Brown, Andrew
  - Sweet Dreams: Philosophical Obstacles to a Science of Consciousness, 2006 -- 2007; MS138.001.003.00027; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Vedomie: Kol'ko jo to v reálnej mene? [Slovak translation of Consciousness: How Much is that in Real Money?], 2006; MS138.001.003.00027.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    - Sweet Dreams: Illusioni filosofiche sulla coscienza [Italian translation of Sweet Dreams: Philosophical Obstacles to a Science of Consciousness], 2006; MS138.001.003.00027.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
    - Sweet Dreams: Illusioni filosofiche sulla coscienza [Italian translation of Sweet Dreams: Philosophical Obstacles to a Science of Consciousness], 2006; MS138.001.003.00027.00003; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
    - Sⱡodkie Sny: Filozoficzne przeszkody na drodze do nauki o świadomości [Polish translation of Sweet Dreams: Philosophical Obstacles to a Science of Consciousness], 2007; MS138.001.003.00027.00004; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
  - Geography Lessons: Letter to the Editor, 2005; MS138.001.003.00028; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Dangerous Ideas: The Sophia Interview With Daniel C. Dennett, 2005; MS138.001.003.00029; Dennett, Daniel C.; Kulic, Anthony (Box 3)
  - Dennetts Dangerous Ideas, 2005; MS138.001.003.00030; Dennett, Daniel C.; Baggini, Julian (Box 3)
  - Moral Issues of Human-Non-Human Primate Neural Grafting, 2005; MS138.001.003.00031; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Show Me The Science, 2005 -- 2006; MS138.001.003.00032; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Show Me The Science, 2005; MS138.001.003.00032.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    - Show Me The Science, 2006; MS138.001.003.00032.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    - The Best American Science and Nature Writing, 2006; MS138.001.003.00032.00004; Greene, Brian (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
  - Comparing Apples to Oranges: Who Does The Framing?, 2005; MS138.001.003.00033; Dennett, Daniel C.; Griffin, Richard (Box 3)
  - Natural Freedom, 2005; MS138.001.003.00034; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    Free will and determinism; Naturalism
  - IDEAS Boston 2005, MS138.001.003.00035; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Ethicists Offer Advice for Testing Human Behavior, 2005; MS138.001.003.00036; Wade, Nicholas (Box 3)
    This article is a response to Moral Issues of Human-Non-Human Primate Neural Grafting.
  - Response to 'What Do You Believe Is True Even Though You Cannot Prove It?', 2005; MS138.001.003.00037; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Response to 'What Do You Believe Is True Even Though You Cannot Prove It?', 2005; MS138.001.003.00037.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    - Daniel C. Dennett, 2005; MS138.001.003.00037.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Breaking the Spell: Religion as a Natural Phenomenon, 2006 -- 2007; MS138.001.003.00038; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Quebrando o encanto: A religião como fenômeno natural [Portuguese translation of Breaking the Spell: Religion as a Natural Phenomenon], 2006; MS138.001.003.00038.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
    - Lumous murtuu: Uskonto luonnonilmiönä [Finnish translation of Breaking the Spell: Religion as a Natural Phenomenon], 2007; MS138.001.003.00038.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
  - Where Ideas Are Born, 2005 -- 2006; MS138.001.003.00039; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Dove nascono le idee [Italian translation of Where Ideas Are Born], 2006; MS138.001.003.00039.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
    - Dove nascono le idee [Italian translation of Where Ideas Are Born], 2006; MS138.001.003.00039.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box data_value_missing_ca701fe8d78187953f592b0c499a65b9)
    - All' ombra di un mito e di strane idee [Italian translation of In the Shadow of a Myth and Strange Ideas], 2005; MS138.001.003.00039.00003; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - From Typo to Thinko: When Evolution Graduated to Semantic Norms, 2006; MS138.001.003.00040; Dennett, Daniel C.; McKay, Ryan
    - From Typo to Thinko: When Evolution Graduated to Semantic Norms, 2006; MS138.001.003.00040.00001; Dennett, Daniel C.; McKay, Ryan (Box 3)
    - From Typo to Thinko: When Evolution Graduated to Semantic Norms, 2006; MS138.001.003.00040.00003; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - Two Steps Closer on Consciousness, 2006; MS138.001.003.00041; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - Two Steps Closer on Consciousness, 2006; MS138.001.003.00041.00001; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    - Two Steps Closer on Consciousness, 2006; MS138.001.003.00041.00002; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
      Connectionism; Materialism; Churchland, Paul M., 1942-
  - Common Sense Religion, 2006; MS138.001.003.00042; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - The Harsh Light of Science: Why a Scientific Study of Religion is Necessary, 2006; MS138.001.003.00043; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - The Future of Religion, 2006; MS138.001.003.00044; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - The Selfish Gene As A Philosophical Essay, 2006; MS138.001.003.00045; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - The Hoax of Intelligent Design and How It Was Perpetrated, 2006; MS138.001.003.00046; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - Toward a Science of Volition, 2006; MS138.001.003.00047; Dennett, Daniel C.; Prinz, Wolfgang; Sebanz, Natalie (Box 3)
    Will; Volition; Philosophy of action; Self-defeating behavior; James, William, 1842-1910
  - Response to Daniel Levine, 2006; MS138.001.003.00048; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - No Vegetables, Please, 2006; MS138.001.003.00049; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - Thank Goodness Not God on Thanksgiving, 2006; MS138.001.003.00050; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - Protecting Democracy Comes Before Promoting Faith, 2006; MS138.001.003.00051; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - Not Yet The Majority But No Longer Silent, 2006; MS138.001.003.00052; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - Daniel C. Dennett Responds to Richard Sosi's review of Breaking the Spell, 2006; MS138.001.003.00053; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
    Religion; Controversial Literature; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - There Arent Enough Minds to House the Population Explosion of Memes, 2006; MS138.001.003.00054; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - A Continuum of Mindfulness, 2006; MS138.001.003.00055; Dennett, Daniel C.; McKay, Ryan
  - How Should We Study Religion?, 2006; MS138.001.003.00056; Dennett, Daniel C.; Swinburne, Richard (Box 3)
  - Religion's Just a Survival Meme: A Response to Alister McGrath, 2006; MS138.001.003.00057; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - A Clever Robot, 2007; MS138.001.003.00058; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - 'God' or 'Allah'?, 2007; MS138.001.003.00059; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - Relying on Faith Instead of Facts Brought Moral Calamity, 2007; MS138.001.003.00060; Dennett, Daniel C.
  - What RoboMary Knows, 2007; MS138.001.003.00061; Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 3)
  - A Daring Reconnaissance of Red Territory: A Review of Seeing Red: A Study in Consciousness, by Nicholas Humphrey, 2007; MS138.001.003.00062; Dennett, Daniel C.
    - A Daring Reconnaissance of Red Territory: A Review of Seeing Red: A Study in Consciousness, by Nicholas Humphrey, 2007; MS138.001.003.00062.00001; Dennett, Daniel C.